Hello friends, I am Kumar Milak, I
welcome you to my channel. So friends, I
hope you all are doing very well.
Sorry, my brother who commented on the
subscribe button, he
commented that if the white wire of this car is cut,
if the wiring of the
car is cut, that is, if it is done, then will
its
insurance be available or not, we are going to
talk about this, so
friends, let's start, so
before starting the video, I would
like to request you that if you
are not on my channel, then subscribe to my channel,
like the video, definitely comment, so the
guide, first of all let me tell you that
if there is a virus in the car and if rats are biting
us, then its insurance,
from my estimation, it does not seem that its insurance, the
clamp in it, will
get
200, as far as
I know, it is being
made, but now we do not know completely whether
its insurance will be available or not.  For
this, you have to
go and talk to your friends there,
after talking there you will get to know
whether the plane will be able to be fixed
or not, so
only after going there you will be able to get the complete information with all the details
because
as far as we think it will not be possible
because of the insurance claims that happen,
but I have the complete
information there right now, otherwise you
can get the complete information from there, so
person we have noticed one thing in this car,
as we told you earlier
in the video that if the steering of your car is new, that is, it is new, then
its steering still gets jammed
and the older your car gets, the more
kilometers you run, the more your steering will keep moving,
or what happened to you is that the
stuffing of the car will get damaged now
and there is no problem in it,
your steering is quite firm as before, it has become
wet but still it
feels great, it used to feel tight while driving,
now look at the one whose  You can, it is very
cool, it is done and so it is gone, as you must have
understood, so come on friend, if you have
understood the video, if you need any information
and width, you can comment us and
we will try our best, so
come on friends, that's all for today, so
come on, I would like to request you again
that if you are not on my channel, then
subscribe to my channel,
like the video, comment and definitely share it, then I can feel that I will meet
you
in the next video with Anil Kapoor and four
wheeler select, if you need any information,
you can comment us,
we will try our best on any video of Gilani,
so come on, that's all for today